<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GreenSnap</string>
    <string name="azaleas">Azaleas</string>
    <string name="azaleas_descripcion">A native Chinese plant of the rhododendron family, it requires careful watering and does not tolerate lime water. Perhaps that is why it survives so little and is one of the biggest challenges for plant lovers. It is a slow-growing plant, usually flowers from April to May, likes cool temperatures and needs watering every other day in hot weather. It also needs to be transplanted outdoors every year.</string>
    <string name="begonias">Begonias</string>
    <string name="begonias_descripcion">Begonias are popular plants because of their beauty and diversity of colours and shapes. They should be cared for in semi-shade, with a draining substrate and moderate watering. The cultivation of begonias is not very difficult. There are more than 2,000 species and under them, numerous varieties. They flower at the beginning of summer and finish their cycle with the first frosts of autumn.</string>
    <string name="cactus">Christmas Cactus</string>
    <string name="cactus_descripcion">It belongs to the Cactaceae family and is a plant native to Central and South America. Although it looks different from most cacti, what differentiates it the most are its flowers, which are shaped like feathers, hence its common name of Santa Teresa\'s feathers, and it flowers earlier than most other species. The flowers can be pink, red, white, orange or yellow and measure between 3 and 5 cm in diameter. It is one of the longest-lasting catus, since in a pot it has a life of between 3 and 10 years. Its cultivation is simple, although it has the disadvantage that some of its segments can be damaged for no apparent reason, so it is necessary to pay attention to its care and eliminate the parts that look bad.</string>
    <string name="calatheas">Calatheas</string>
    <string name="calatheas_descripcion">It is a tropical plant of the marantas family, depending on the species, the plant adopts different sizes, colours and shapes in its leaves. The leaves are born rolled and then open, the stems grow in clusters, they are perennial and their leaves have an ability called nioctinasia, where the leaves open during the day to seek the sun and close at night to reduce water loss.</string>
    <string name="crassula">Crassula</string>
    <string name="crassula_descripcion">It belongs to the family of thick-leaved plants (Crassulaceae). It also belongs to the subfamily Crassuloideae. This tree grows to a maximum height of approximately 3 metres. It has a thick, straight stem and many branches. At its base, it is often strongly branched. It is a well-known succulent plant everywhere and is very easy to obtain, grows easily and is fairly easy to care for.</string>
    <string name="dionaea">Dionaea Muscipula</string>
    <string name="dionaea_descripcion">Called Diana flytrap in some countries such as South America and more commonly known as Venus flytrap, it is one of the most emblematic types of carnivorous plants. It is the only species in the genus Dionaea, which originated in North Carolina. Its leaves grow from a buried rhizome, forming a rosette with a length of between 3cm and 8cm, growing horizontally. At flowering time in spring, it gives rise to a flowering stem growing from the very centre of the plant, which is up to 20cm high and with a striking small white flower at the tip.</string>
    <string name="echeveria">Echeveria</string>
    <string name="echeveria_descripcion">Also called alabaster rose, it is actually a whole genus of succulent plants that forms part of the Crassulaceae family. It is native to Mexico and Brazil, with about 400 species, very resistant to drought conditions and thermal variations, its stems reach heights of up to 20cm and it produces pink or yellowish flowers from winter to spring.</string>
    <string name="euphorbia">Euphorbia</string>
    <string name="euphorbia_descripcion">It is commonly known as the crown of Christ plant or crown of thorns plant because there is a legend that this was the plant used to make the crown of thorns. It is originally from Madagascar, a shrub that can reach, or even exceed, heights of 1 metre and stands out for the red or pink bracts of its flowers, which are very striking. It is a very hardy succulent plant, which can flower all year round in the right climate and conditions.</string>
    <string name="guzmania">Guzmania (Francesca)</string>
    <string name="guzmania_descripcion">It is one of the most beautiful and unusual houseplants to be found and is very popular, not only for its beauty, but also for its easy care. Its leaves, like its inflorescence, are highly decorative.</string>
    <string name="claveles">Carnations</string>
    <string name="claveles_descripcion">They are native to Eurasia, and have become a symbol of many Mediterranean countries because of their beauty. They are perennial herbs that bloom during spring and summer, among which a great variety of colours and shapes can be found.</string>
    <string name="margaritas">Margarite</string>
    <string name="margaritas_descripcion">They are one of the most popular plants in the world and their flowers are so characteristic. They are extremely prolific, and there are more than 140 different species.</string>
    <string name="violas">Violas</string>
    <string name="violas_descripcion">Also called pansy plants, they are native to northern Europe and currently have an enormous number of varieties, with different types of flower colours and sizes. They need a very luminous area and keep the soil moist without puddling (in bloom they are watered every 2 or 3 days). It is edible, it flowers in autumn and in warm climates its flowering can extend until spring.</string>
    <string name="azalea_hortinno">Azalea Hortinno</string>
    <string name="azalea_hortinno_noralinde">Azalea Hortinno Noralinde</string>
    <string name="azalea_hortinno_yankadi">Azalea Hortinno Yankadi</string>
    <string name="azalea_piramide">Azalea Pyramid</string>
    <string name="begonia_elatior_roja_baladin">Begonia Elatior Red (Baladin)</string>
    <string name="begonia_elatior_roja_grace">Begonia Elatior Red (Grace)</string>
    <string name="begonia_elatior_salmon">Begonia Elatior Salmon (Borias)</string>
    <string name="begonia_maculata">Begonia Maculata (Wightii)</string>
    <string name="cactus_navidad">"Schlumbergera "</string>
    <string name="calathea_lancifolia">Calathea Lancifolia</string>
    <string name="calathea_ornata">Calathea Ornata (Sanderiana)</string>
    <string name="calathea_roseopicta">Calathea Roseopicta (Medallion)</string>
    <string name="calathea_zebrina">Calathea Zebrina</string>
    <string name="crassula_ovata">Crassula Ovata</string>
    <string name="dionaea_muscipula">"Dionaea Muscipula "</string>
    <string name="echeveria_pulvinata">Echeveria Pulvinata</string>
    <string name="euphorbia_milii">"Euphorbia Milii "</string>
    <string name="guzmania_francesca">Guzmania (Francesca)</string>
    <string name="dianthus_barbatus">Dianthus Barbatus</string>
    <string name="dianthus_caryophyllus">Dianthus Caryophyllus</string>
    <string name="dimorphotheca_ecklonis">Dimorphoteca Ecklonis</string>
    <string name="viola_x_wittrockiana">"Viola x Wittrockiana "</string>
    <string name="interior">indoor</string>
    <string name="exterior">outer</string>
    <string name="ambos">both</string>
    <string name="luz">Lighting</string>
    <string name="temperatura">Temperature</string>
    <string name="sustrato">Substrate</string>
    <string name="riego">Irrigation</string>
    <string name="humedad">Humidity</string>
    <string name="abono">Fertiliser</string>
    <string name="poda">Pruning</string>
    <string name="enfermedades">Diseases</string>
    <string name="transplante">Trasplanting</string>
    <string name="luz_azalea">Places with indirect light, especially in the middle of the day. A place near a window facing east or west is ideal.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_azalea">Between 13-15ºC</string>
    <string name="sustrato_azalea">It needs an acidic, well-drained substrate. You can mix peat moss, athena and perlite to ensure good drainage and moisture retention.</string>
    <string name="riego_azalea">Keep the potting soil moist but not wet. Water when the top layer of the substrate is dry to the touch with non-alkaline water (you can filter or collect rainwater). Avoid waterlogging and over-watering as this can cause disease and rotting of the plant. Water every 2 days in hot weather.</string>
    <string name="humedad_azalea">The plant needs a very humid environment, so you can place the pot on a plate full of water with stones that will prevent the pot from touching the water, or spray the leaves with distilled water.</string>
    <string name="abono_azalea">Apply a specific fertiliser for acidophilic plants during the growing season (spring-summer) every 2-4 weeks following the manufacturer\'s instructions to avoid burning the roots.</string>
    <string name="poda_azalea">Use sharp, smooth tools to avoid tearing branches and the spread of disease. Make cuts just above a bud at a 45-degree angle. Remove any dead, diseased or damaged branches, as well as those that are intertwined in the centre of the plant to allow better air circulation and light to enter. It requires a rest period to flower again, so it should be placed in a cool place (13-15ºC) for 6-8 weeks, avoiding cold draughts and sudden changes in temperature.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_azalea">It is often susceptible to pests such as aphids, spider mites and mealy bugs, as well as fungal diseases. Regularly inspect your plant and treat any infestations or diseases with appropriate products.</string>
    <string name="trasplante_azalea">An annual transplanting is necessary outdoors. During the summer in a shady place at the beginning of June we make a hole big enough for the plant to fit in its pot (pot included), controlling watering and humidity even more. At the beginning of September it is dug up and if we see that the roots protrude from underneath, we change to a bigger pot with great care.</string>
    <string name="luz_begonia">Place it near a window. Avoid exposing it to direct sunlight as this can burn its leaves.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_begonia">Requires a warm and stable temperature (18-24°C). Avoid cold draughts and intense heat sources such as radiators.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_begonia">Use a well-drained substrate rich in organic matter. You can mix potting soil with peat or perlite to improve texture and drainage.</string>
    <string name="riego_begonia">Does not tolerate standing water. Allow topsoil to dry out before watering again. Control substrate moisture and avoid over-watering.</string>
    <string name="humedad_begonia">It likes humidity, so it is advisable to place a saucer with water near the pot or use a humidifier in dry environments.</string>
    <string name="abono_begonia">Use a balanced liquid fertiliser for begonias once a month during the growing season (spring-summer). Follow the manufacturer\'s instructions to avoid over-fertilising and damaging the roots.</string>
    <string name="poda_begonia">Remove wilted flowers and yellowing leaves to promote healthy growth. Do this with clean, sharp tools.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_begonia">It is susceptible to pests such as spider mites, aphids, and mealy bugs. Regularly inspect your plant using organic insecticides if necessary and avoid excess moisture to prevent fungal diseases.</string>
    <string name="trasplante_begonia">It is not necessary until the roots come out of the pot, in which case move to a larger pot very carefully. Try to do this in spring.</string>
    <string name="luz_cactus">It needs to be in a place where it receives partial shade, so a window is the best option. If you put it outdoors in summer, it should be kept out of direct sunlight.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_cactus">Between 15-22ºC</string>
    <string name="sustrato_cactus">Use a well-drained, nutrient-rich substrate. You can do this with a mixture of mulched peat or heath soil and perlite, vermiculite or volcanic gravel to improve drainage.</string>
    <string name="riego_cactus">It needs an average of 2 waterings per week, especially during the growing season (spring-summer). The rest of the year it should be watered less frequently.</string>
    <string name="humedad_cactus">At least 50%, which can be achieved by spraying the leaves every 2-3 days when the environment is dry.</string>
    <string name="abono_cactus">Apply in spring and summer by adding liquid fertiliser to irrigation once a month (following the manufacturer\'s instructions).</string>
    <string name="poda_cactus">This plant does not need pruning, but you will need to remove bad or damaged leaves. Use clean, sharp tools.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_cactus">Aphids and mealy bugs are the ones that affect this plant the most, and you can eliminate them with a mixture of water and soap.</string>
    <string name="trasplante_cactus">This should be done in the spring and every two years, always using a larger pot so that it can grow without problems during those two years.</string>
    <string name="luz_calatheas">They need a bright room, but keep them away from windows and direct light sources. In winter move it to a place where it gets more light. If you notice that the leaves dry out or show brown spots, it is getting too much light. Avoid placing it near cookers, fireplaces or radiators.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_calatheas">Between 16-21°C in warm months and don\'t let it drop below 13°C in winter. If it drops below 10ºC you may lose it.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_calatheas">Good drainage is very important. It is best to use the universal seedling mix (peat, coco fibre and worm castings in equal parts, and add a handful of vermiculite and a handful of perlite to promote drainage.</string>
    <string name="riego_calatheas">Two or three times a week in small amounts to maintain humidity and prevent root rot. In warm months do not let the top layer of the substrate dry out, in winter you can let it dry out slightly.</string>
    <string name="humedad_calatheas">It needs a very high level of humidity, so you should spray the leaves from time to time or put the pot on a plate of water and stones to avoid contact with water (you should change the water a couple of times a week) or put it in the bathroom, as it is usually very bright and the humidity level is very high.</string>
    <string name="abono_calatheas">You can add 1 or 2cm of worm humus to the base of the stems once a month during the growing season (April-September).</string>
    <string name="poda_calatheas">It is not necessary to prune, only to remove withered or diseased leaves.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_calatheas">If the leaves are burnt, it is because of too much light, if they are yellow, it is because of lack of nutrients or lack of light, and if the leaves are darker in colour, it is because of too much water. It is prone to red spider mites, which manifest themselves by weakening the leaves and fine webs. It can also be infested with sandy bugs or waxy insects.</string>
    <string name="transplante_calatheas">When the roots protrude from the pot, carefully move to a larger pot.</string>
    <string name="luz_crassula">It requires full sun, but can also tolerate indirect light. A striking red border on the leaves can be seen and flowers can also develop when in full sun. Under shade these two special characteristics are not visible.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_crassula">"Between 12-26ºC. Not recommended for outdoor areas where there is frost (it can withstand frosts down to -2ºC without flinching, but with a dry substrate to avoid damage to the roots). "</string>
    <string name="sustrato_crassula">"It needs a substrate that drains well and retains water to some extent. You can make a mixture of equal parts of perlite, vermiculite and tepojal with peat. "</string>
    <string name="riego_crassula">"It needssubstrate, you must wait until it is dry before watering again. moderate watering. What tells us when to water is the substrate, you should wait until it is dry before watering again. "</string>
    <string name="humedad_crassula">Requires low humidity, rather low.</string>
    <string name="abono_crassula">This plant does not need many nutrients for its development, so it is recommended to use liquid fertiliser 2-3 times during the growing season (spring-summer-autumn).</string>
    <string name="poda_crassula">When the plant is more than 1 year old you should remove the branches that are too thin and too long to support the weight of the leaves, this way new thicker branches will grow, which will allow the plant to be taller and wider (you will notice when you should do this when the branches start to droop downwards). You should do this in spring or early summer.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_crassula">The biggest enemy of this plant is humidity. Excessive watering, especially if you eat it in cold temperatures, will cause its roots to rot and encourage the appearance of fungus. As far as pests are concerned, its leaves are a meal for mealy bugs. Although an invasion of these insects does not usually endanger the life of the plant, it is advisable to eliminate them as soon as possible by applying a suitable phytosanitary product. (It is also susceptible to attack by aphids.</string>
    <string name="trasplante_crassula">The best time is during spring or summer. Water the substrate lightly to facilitate extraction. Once outside, examine the roots and remove any dead or rotten roots. Place a thin layer of new substrate in the bottom of the container and place the jade tree in the centre and fill with substrate until all the roots are covered. Press down lightly on the substrate to settle it. Avoid watering immediately, you should wait at least a week to allow the roots to adapt to their new environment. After a week, water moderately, avoiding waterlogging.</string>
    <string name="luz_dionaea">It needs a lot of sunlight, so a window facing east or west is ideal. If you can\'t, you can use a plant lamp. If you put it outdoors it is best if it has partial shade, it can get direct sun but only when it has become accustomed to the climate of the area and your care.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_dionaea">Between 20-35ºC. In winter it should be kept above 0ºC. Avoid draughts.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_dionaea">This plant needs an acidic and moisture retentive substrate. This is achieved with a mixture of coconut fibre, perlite and sphagnum moss.</string>
    <string name="riego_dionaea">Always water with distilled or rain water. Always keep the soil moist. It should be watered by reverse irrigation, i.e. leaving a finger of water in the pot plate, which will keep the substrate moist by capillary action. The ideal method is to leave a finger of water in the pot at all times until it is completely consumed, leave to stand for two days and repeat the process.</string>
    <string name="humedad_dionaea">It needs high humidity, preferably without spraying. You can use a saucer with water near the pot or place a small glass or plastic dome to seal it.</string>
    <string name="abono_dionaea">We should not fertilise it, as traditional fertilisers would burn its roots. What replaces its fertiliser, and acts as such, is the capture of the insects it catches. There is no need for us to capture its prey as the plant has developed a natural method of attracting them on its own. If we still can\'t resist the temptation we should give it live insects as their movement when caught is what triggers the release of the plant\'s gastric juices. We must also be careful when setting their traps frequently by mistake or for amusement, as the closing of the traps causes a lot of stress to the plant and can kill it.</string>
    <string name="poda_dionaea">This should be done in the spring as it is beginning its growth cycle and allows it to recover quickly and concentrate its energy on new growth. We examine the plant to identify any blackened, brown traps or traps showing signs of damage, remove the material with well disinfected and sharp tools, and dispose of the removed material away from the plant to avoid any possible disease or attraction of decaying pests.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_dionaea">This plant is mainly affected by leaf rot (a fungal disease that causes wilting and death of its leaves), brown spot (a fungal disease that causes brown spots on its leaves, causing the leaves to die and is even capable of inhibiting the plant\'s ability to trap insects), leaf wilt (a disease caused by excess water or pests, characterised by progressive wilting of the plant).</string>
    <string name="trasplante_dionaea">The right time is in spring or early summer. Ideally, it should be repotted every 2-3 years, or when the plant outgrows its current container size.</string>
    <string name="luz_echeveria">It needs full sun exposure. It can also be kept in semi-shade if it receives a few hours of full sun during the day, or indoors if placed near a window.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_echeveria">Between 18-26ºC. It can withstand up to 0ºC when the substrate is dry for 1-2 days, although this is best avoided.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_echeveria">It must be draining, as water retention is taken care of by the leaves. You can prepare a mixture of substrate for succulents or cacti with equal parts of earthworm humus, peat and a porous material such as vemiculite, tepojal or volcanic gravel.</string>
    <string name="riego_echeveria">As it stores water in its leaf tissue, it is a low watering plant, so it should be watered when the first centimetre of the substrate dries out. In winter it is best to water every two weeks to prevent the leaves from shrivelling. It should not be watered above the rosette as this will cause rotting. The method of watering is by immersion, where the pot is submerged in a container with water so that it can absorb what it needs, as watering on the substrate is usually more difficult due to the wide growth of this species.</string>
    <string name="humedad_echeveria">Avoid a humid environment, as this makes the plant more susceptible to fungal diseases.</string>
    <string name="abono_echeveria">A low nitrogen fertiliser can be applied in spring and summer, although it is not essential.</string>
    <string name="poda_echeveria">Pruning is not strictly necessary, but if you notice dead or damaged leaves, you can remove them to keep the plant healthy. Always in the growing season (spring-summer).</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_echeveria">"The most common pests that can affect this plant are aphids and mealybugs, which you can eliminate by applying natural insecticide or insecticidal soap for aphids and use a cotton swab soaked in isopropyl alcohol for mealybugs. The most common diseases affecting this plant are root rot due to overwatering and grey mould due to excess humidity (to treat grey mould you can use fungicides specific for succulent plants). "</string>
    <string name="trasplante_echeveria">This should be done in spring or summer if the plant has outgrown its current pot size or if there are signs of deterioration in the quality of the substrate (the substrate is compacted and does not facilitate drainage).</string>
    <string name="luz_euphorbia">It needs direct sunlight and will flower abundantly as long as it receives three or four hours of sunlight during the day. Outdoors, try to place it in full sun, indoors, during the winter, place the plant in a south or west-facing spot.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_euphorbia">Between 18-23°C. It can tolerate night temperatures down to 10ºC.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_euphorbia">If planted outdoors, plant in well-drained soil. If planted indoors, it needs a well-drained cacti substrate mix (peat with mulch or heath soil with perlite, vermiculite or volcanic gravel). It should not be planted in a container larger than the root ball and excess soil will retain water and may cause the roots to rot.</string>
    <string name="riego_euphorbia">It does not require much water. Outdoors, rain water will suffice, in pots, we will water when the substrate dries out completely. Do this abundantly and let all the excess water drain away, avoiding waterlogging and keeping the substrate damp for long periods of time. During the winter it hardly needs watering.</string>
    <string name="humedad_euphorbia">Generally below 50%, so it needs a rather low humidity level. A sprayer should be used every 3-4 days.</string>
    <string name="abono_euphorbia">Use a balanced liquid fertiliser for indoor plants from spring to autumn, fertilising it with water a couple of times a month.</string>
    <string name="poda_euphorbia">It does not need pruning, but you can remove withered leaves and branches in autumn, so that next season it will stimulate its growth.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_euphorbia">It is not prone to pests and diseases, but it can still suffer from the most common houseplant problems such as aphids or mealy bugs (these can be eliminated with home remedies). It can also suffer from fungal diseases such as brotitis which causes leaf spots or root rot (let the soil dry out before watering again, this is the best way to prevent this problem).</string>
    <string name="trasplante_euphorbia">When the plant is too big, move it carefully to another pot or to the garden as you prefer, in any case you need a well-drained substrate.</string>
    <string name="luz_guzmania">Requires indirect and abundant light. Place near a window with light curtains to filter the sun\'s rays.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_guzmania">Between 18-24ºC. Avoid exposure to cold draughts or extreme heat.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_guzmania">Use a light, well-drained mixture of peat, perlite and coconut fibre. This will ensure good drainage and prevent waterlogging of the roots.</string>
    <string name="riego_guzmania">It needs constant but moderate watering. The substrate should always be kept slightly damp, avoiding waterlogging. It is important to water directly on the leaves and not in the centre of the rosette, to avoid waterlogging the roots.</string>
    <string name="humedad_guzmania">It needs a humid environment. The humidity can be increased by placing the pot on a dish with water and stones or by using a humidifier.</string>
    <string name="abono_guzmania">During the growing season (spring-summer), we can fertilise it once a month using balanced liquid fertiliser according to the manufacturer\'s instructions.</string>
    <string name="poda_guzmania">It can be pruned at any time of the year, however, it is important to make sure that the plant is not too stressed by environmental factors or diseases before pruning.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_guzmania">The diseases and pests that most affect this species are leaf spot (a fungal disease that causes spots or discolourations on the leaves), root rot (weak or damaged roots, causing the leaves to wilt, or the plant to turn brown and the base to soften), mealy bugs (small insects that appear as white spots or gries on the leaves) and mites (small and difficult to see with the naked eye, but the leaves become discoloured or look dry).</string>
    <string name="trasplante_guzmania">This should be done in mid to late spring. This allows the plant to take root before summer and gives it the opportunity to grow and strengthen to withstand it.</string>
    <string name="luz_dianthus">It needs a good amount of direct sunlight to flower properly. Place your plant in a place where it receives at least 6 hours of sunlight a day.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_dianthus">Between 15-35ºC. It can withstand a minimum temperature of -10ºC in winter and a maximum of 45ºC in summer.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_dianthus">It needs a slightly alkaline but clay-free soil with good drainage.</string>
    <string name="riego_dianthus">Be sure to water the plant when the top layer of soil is dry, avoiding any runners that could damage the roots.</string>
    <string name="humedad_dianthus">It is advisable to maintain a moderate level, avoiding excessive humidity or a dry environment. A sprayer can be used for this purpose.</string>
    <string name="abono_dianthus">Apply a flowering plant fertiliser or compost in spring to stimulate flowering, especially in the case of pot carnations.</string>
    <string name="poda_dianthus">Regular pruning is important to keep the carnation in good shape. Remove faded flowers and dead or weakened branches to encourage healthy growth.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_dianthus">Pests and diseases affecting this plant are slugs (they feed on all parts of the plant), thrips (they feed on the underside of the leaves, like very small black scissors), aphids (they are red, green or brown in colour and feed on the cells of the leaves and flower buds), European tortrix (a lepidopteran whose larvae feed on the flowers), leafminers (dipterans whose larvae dig galleries in the leaves), leafminers (diptera whose larvae burrow galleries in the leaves), rust (a fungal disease that causes orange-coloured spots on leaves and stems), fusarium (a fungal disease that rots the roots and weakens the stem) and carnation spotted carnation virus (a virus that causes small brown or purple spots in lines or rings).</string>
    <string name="trasplante_dianthus">They are done from March-May, May-June and in autumn, although they can be done at other times of the year as long as the temperature, humidity and luminosity are controlled.</string>
    <string name="luz_dimorphotheca">These beautiful plants have to be placed in full sun, otherwise they may not flower, otherwise the flowers will not open properly.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_dimorphotheca">Pleasant temperature around 20ºC. It can tolerate -5ºC in winter with a completely dry substrate.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_dimorphotheca">It is important that the soil in which it is planted is able to absorb water. You can use universal mixed with perlite. If it has drainage problems, we must take measures, installing drainage systems: make a planting hole of 50x50cm (I recommend 1x1m if your garden usually floods when it rains a lot or torrentially), cover its sides (except the base) with shading netting and place a thick layer, at least 20cm, of arlite or volcanic clay. Then finish filling with universal substrate.</string>
    <string name="riego_dimorphotheca">It has to be watered every 2-3 days in summer, and 1-2 times a week the rest of the year.</string>
    <string name="humedad_dimorphotheca">Avoid excess and lack of moisture, it must be level.</string>
    <string name="abono_dimorphotheca">This should be done during the growing season (spring-autumn). Any universal garden fertiliser can be used.</string>
    <string name="poda_dimorphotheca">Pruning is not necessary, but damaged, diseased or wilted leaves should be removed to encourage healthy growth.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_dimorphotheca">It can be attacked by aphids. If this happens, you can either wait for the sun to warm up and the heat itself will kill the pest, or you can solve the problem with ecological treatments such as potassium soap or Neem oil. It is strongly recommended that you solve the problem yourself as soon as you see any signs of it.</string>
    <string name="trasplante_dimorphoteca">It is important that it receives direct sunlight throughout the day, so it should not be placed near plants or other shady elements. It is best done in spring.</string>
    <string name="luz_violas">It is important to place them in very luminous areas, where they receive a good amount of sunlight. If the climate is very hot or the sun is very intense, it is advisable to place them in shade.</string>
    <string name="temperatura_violas">It withstands a very wide range of temperatures, from the warmest to not too intense frosts.</string>
    <string name="sustrato_violas">They need a fairly nutrient-rich soil. You can use peat along with vemiculite and perlite for good drainage.</string>
    <string name="riego_violas">During the flowering period, watering every 2-3 days will be necessary depending on the specific characteristics of the climate and soil. For the rest of the year, the soil should always be kept relatively moist, but never waterlogged. Excessive watering or insufficiently drained soil could lead to excess moisture in the roots, causing the plant to become sick or weak.</string>
    <string name="humedad_violas">It needs an environment with balanced humidity. This can be achieved by placing the pot on a dish with water and stones or with a sprayer.</string>
    <string name="abono_violas">Worm humus is recommended for its composition, which is very beneficial for both the plant and the soil.</string>
    <string name="poda_violas">It tends to lose much of its vitality when the warmer months arrive after flowering, and it is not uncommon for the plant to die if nothing is done. To avoid this, and to get our flower to live as a perennial instead of a biennial, it will be necessary to prune it aggressively as soon as the temperatures rise, leaving only the stem.</string>
    <string name="enfermedades_violas">One of the main threats to this plant is the attack of aphids and fungi such as powdery mildew, which is the one to watch out for.</string>
    <string name="trasplante_violas">The perfect period is during autumn-spring allowing the plant to establish strong roots before the heat of summer.</string>
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="inicio">Home</string>
    <string name="web">Web</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
</resources>